Guide to the Newberg Friend Cemetery records 1879-1998
George Fox University and Northwest Yearly Meeting of Friends Archives
Newberg Friends Cemetery records
1879-1998
George Fox University and Northwest Yearly Meeting of Friends Archives 416 North Meridian Street Newberg, Oregon 97132 archives@georgefox.edu http://www.georgefox.edu/offices/murdock/Archives/index.html
Newberg Friends Church (1893-)
NWYM.01.21
.5 cubic feet
Records of burials, correspondence, treasurers records, and other information about Newberg Friends Cemetery.
Accession Leg.812
Records of burials, correspondence, treasurers records, and other information about Newberg Friends Cemetery. Also includes some information about the adjacent GAR cemetery, and Fernwood Pioneer Cemetery.
This collection is available for research.
Quakers
Religion
- Fernwood Pioneer Cemetery: Nomination for Historic Places, 1993; 1/1; 1 folders
- Correspondence, 1966-1974; 1/2; 1 folders
- Wilder, Lori, 1985-1988; 1/3; 1 folders
- Treasurer's Reports, 1965-1967; 1/4; 1 folders
- Persons Buried in Newberg Cemetery: A-F, 1906-1926; 1/5; 1 folders
- Persons Buried in Newberg Cemetery: G-M, 1906-1926; 1/6; 1 folders
- Persons Buried in Newberg Cemetery: N-S, 1906-1926; 1/7; 1 folders
- Persons Buried in Newberg Cemetery: T-Z Plus Miscellaneous Names, 1906-1926; 1/8; 1 folders
- Persons Buried in Newberg Cemetery: A-G, 1901-1933; 1/9; 1 folders
- Persons Buried in Newberg Friends Cemetery, 1901-1933; 1/10; 1 folders
- Persons Buried in Newberg Friends Cemetery, 1901-1933; 1/11; 1 folders
- Deed and History, 1879-1998; 1/12; 1 folders
- Ledger, 1950; 1/13; 1 folders
- Cemetery Records, 1940; 1/14; 1 folders